[
    {
      "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
      "options": ["2", "4", "6"],
      "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 5 + 7?",
      "options": ["6", "12", "31"],
      "correctAnswer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 15 + 27?",
      "options": ["36", "315", "42"],
      "correctAnswer": "42"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 51 + 117?",
      "options": ["168", "531", "110"],
      "correctAnswer": "168"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 151 + 1111?",
      "options": ["2544", "831", "1262"],
      "correctAnswer": "1262"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10 - 3?",
      "options": ["5", "7", "10"],
      "correctAnswer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 25 - 12?",
      "options": ["13", "12", "7"],
      "correctAnswer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 50 - 30?",
      "options": ["20", "40", "50"],
      "correctAnswer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 100 - 78?",
      "options": ["22", "78", "100"],
      "correctAnswer": "22"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 8 * 4?",
      "options": ["32", "12", "16"],
      "correctAnswer": "32"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 12 * 3?",
      "options": ["36", "15", "24"],
      "correctAnswer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 25 * 2?",
      "options": ["40", "50", "70"],
      "correctAnswer": "50"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 16 * 5?",
      "options": ["80", "40", "70"],
      "correctAnswer": "80"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 100 / 5?",
      "options": ["25", "50", "20"],
      "correctAnswer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 49 / 7?",
      "options": ["7", "14", "6"],
      "correctAnswer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 81 / 9?",
      "options": ["9", "18", "27"],
      "correctAnswer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 144 / 12?",
      "options": ["14", "12", "18"],
      "correctAnswer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 63 / 9?",
      "options": ["7", "9", "14"],
      "correctAnswer": "7"
    }
  ]
  